pscsoftware.com 2018-12-28

# Privacy Statement | PSC Software

This site is owned and operated by PSC Biotech. Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. At PSC, we want to make your experience online satisfying and safe 

Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we feel you should fully understand our policy and the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it. 

* * *

## Information We Gather and Track

PSC gathers two types of information about users: 

  * Information that users provided through optional, voluntary submissions. These are voluntary submissions to receive our electronic documentation, requesting a software demo, and from participation in surveys.

  * Information PSC gathers through aggregated tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views throughout our sites. This information allows us to better tailor our content to readers' needs and to help our advertisers and sponsors better understand the demographics of our audience. Under no circumstances does PSC divulge any information about an individual user to a third party.

PSC gathers user infromation in the following processes:

**Children**

Consistent with the Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without requesting parental consent. 

**Usage Tracking**

PSC tracks user traffic patterns throughout all of our sites. However, we do not correlate this information with data about individual users. PSC does break down overall usage statistics according to a user's domain name, browser type, and MIME type by reading this information from the browser string (information contained in every user's browser). 

**Cookies**

We may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain Personal Information although it will enable us to relate your use of this site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. PSC uses cookies to track user traffic patterns (as described above). 

You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you've set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use this site. However, you do need cookies to view electronic documentation after successful registration. 

* * *

## Use of Information

PSC uses any information voluntarily given by our users to enhance their experience in our network of sites, whether to provide interactive or personalized elements on the sites or to better prepare future content based on the interests of our users. 

As stated above, we use information that users voluntarily provide in order to allow for electronic documentation download and requesting a software demo. PSC never shares users personal information with any third parties, including advertisers, sponsors or partners. 

When we use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you. 

PSC creates aggregate reports on user demographics and traffic patterns for advertisers, sponsors and partners. This allows our advertisers to advertise more effectively, and allows our users to receive advertisements that are pertinent to their needs. Because we don't track the usage patterns of individual users, an advertiser or sponsor will never know that a specific user clicked their ad. We will not disclose any information about any individual user except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public. 

* * *

## Sharing of the Information

PSC uses the above-described information to tailor our content to suit your needs and help our advertisers better understand our audience's demographics. We will not share information about individual users with any third party, except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public. 

* * *

## Security

PSC operates secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by our customers. 

* * *

## Your Consent

By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by PSC. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
